Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. International Advertisements Collection, 1900-2004 and undated, bulk 1965-1990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Europe Series, 1900-2002 and undated (Box CA30)
  - Italy (Box EU4)
    - Milan Office (Box EU4)
      - [Rizzoli Editore: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU5)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box EU5)
      - Sitia Yomo (Yomo Yomi) yogurt, 1987 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - [Standard Brands: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU5)
      - Unilever (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
        - Bizaine perfume, 1982 (Box EU5)
        - Clear shampoo, 1985 (Box EU5)
        - Executive cologne, 1980 (Box EU5)
    - Rome Office (Box EU5)
      - Alitalia airline, 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - Citicorp (Diners Club International Card), 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - IRI Group (Raggruppamento Selenia Elsag), 1985 (Box EU5)
    - Undetermined Office (Box EU5)
      - Fini Pasta, 1998-2002 (Box EU5)
      - Kraft (Jacobs, Jocca, Philadelphia Cream Cheese), 1998-2002 (Box EU5)
      - Negroni Ham, 1998-2002 (Box EU5)
  - Netherlands (Amsterdam Office) (Box EU5)
    - Agio Signarenbreiken (Red Labee) cigars, 1981 (Box EU5)
    - Algemene Bank Nederland, 1982 (Box EU5)
    - Amsterdamse Effectenbeurs, 1984 (Box EU5)
    - [BMW: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU5)
    - Chevron car care products, 1982 (Box EU5)
    - Eastman Kodak (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - Ektra, 1981 (Box EU5)
      - Instomatic, circa 1970 (Box EU5)
      - Signet Kopiees photocopier, undated (Box EU5)
    - Ford (Box EU5)
      - Capri, 1960s (Box EU5)
      - Escort, 1960s (Box EU5)
      - Fiesta, 1981 (Box EU5)
      - Taunus, 1960s, 1981 (Box EU5)
      - Trucks, undated (Box EU5)
    - Frans Verbant and Company (Black and White) scotch whiskey, circa 1969-1970 (Box EU5)
    - Kellogg Company (Box EU5)
      - Cornflakes, 1960s (Box EU5)
      - Honey Smacks, 1960s (Box EU5)
      - Rice Krispies, 1960s (Box EU5)
      - Smacks, 1960s, 1982, 1984 (Box EU5)
    - Kluwer Publishing, Van Dale dictionaries, 1984 (Box EU5)
    - Mattel (Masters of the Universe), late 1980s (Box EU5)
    - Miscellaneous cheeses (St. Moret Linesse, Mon Chou, Paturain Linesse), 1999 (Box EU5)
    - Nutricia (Olvarit) baby food, 1969, 1982 (Box EU5)
    - Nutroma tea, 1981 (Box EU5)
    - Outboard Marine (Evinrude), 1970 (Box EU5)
    - Philips, 1965 (Box EU5)
      [Cover art for Philips' recording artist Ronnie Tober single Zonder Jou b/w Verboden Vruchten, Philips no. JF-327-860, 1965]
    - Primair Bereik, 1981 (Box EU5)
    - Rolex, 1986 (Box EU5)
    - Unilever (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU5)
      - Calve peanut butter, 1982, 1984 (Box EU5)
      - Lux soap and detergent, 1960s, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box EU5)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box EU5)
      - Benylin cold medicine, 1988 (Box EU5)
      - Elase first aid medicine, 1988 (Box EU5)
      - Listerine, 1988 (Box EU5)
      - Rami cough syrup, 1988 (Box EU5)
  - Norway (Oslo Office) (Box EU5)
    - Eastman Kodak consumer, 1968 (Box EU6)
    - Rolex, 1986 (Box EU6)
  - Poland (Warsaw Office) (Box EU6)
    - General Motors (Chevrolet, LaSalle, from microfilm), 1920s (Box EU6)
  - Portugal (Lisbon Office) (Box EU6)
    - A.L.C. Perafita (Longa Vita) Camembert cheese, 1987 (Box EU6)
    - António Pacheco Agostino, 1991 (Box EU6)
    - BDF, 1991 (Box EU6)
    - Copaz (Box EU6)
      - Generic soy oil advertisements, 1987, 1990 (Box EU6)
      - Ibersoja soy oil, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box EU6)
    - Cortal office furniture, 1988, 1990 (Box EU6)
    - Elida Gibbs (Denim), 1991 (Box EU6)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1987 (Box EU6)
    - Kraft (Philadelphia Cream Cheese), 1999 (Box EU6)
    - Levi Strauss (with documentation), 1974 (Box EU6)
    - Lisgrafica, Noticia Lisgrafica magazine, 1988 (Box EU6)
    - Luso American Foundation (Vianna de Motta Piano contest program), 1987 (Box EU6)
    - Montpio Geral financial services, 1990 (Box EU6)
    - Nestlé-Findus, 1992 (Box EU6)
    - [Proleite/Mimosa (UNICEF): See Oversize Folder OF12] (Box EU6)
    - Refrigor, 1992 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU6)
    - Scott Paper, 1992 (Box EU6)
    - Secretaria Do Estado Da Cultura, Direccao Geral da Accao Cultural theater campaign, 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU6)
    - Setron Ltd. (Pioneer) stereo equipment, 1984 (Box EU6)
    - [Sogrape (Mateus): See Oversize Folder OF12] (Box EU6)
    - Telecom Portugal, 1990 (Box EU6)
    - Telecommunicasoes CTT, 1990 (Box EU6)
    - Triunfo pasta, 1990 (Box EU6)
    - Unilever (Box EU6)
      - Coral laundry detergent, 1987-1988 (Box EU6)
        [Includes pattern books]
      - Mentadent toothpaste, 1989 (Box EU6)
      - News Sunsilk Hair Care, 1988 (Box EU6)
        [Magazine for hairdressers]
      - Sunsilk hair care products, 1984, 1987 (Box EU6)
      - Various (Includes Linic, Mexina, Pepsodentfluor), 1984, 1988 (Box EU6)
  - Romania (Bucharest Office) (Box EU6)
    - [Jacobs: See Oversize Folder OF13] (Box EU6)
    - [Tragerile Loterei de State: See Oversize Folder OF13] (Box EU6)
  - Russia (Undetermined Office) (Box EU6)
    - Jacobs, 1998-1999 (Box EU6)
  - Slovak Republic (Undetermined Office) (Box EU6)
    - Jacobs, 1998-1999 (Box EU6)
  - Slovenia (Served by JWT Bucharest) (Box EU6)
    - General Motors (Opel Six, from microfilm), 1920s (Box EU6)
  - Spain (Box EU6)
    - Barcelona Office (Box EU6)
      - Allied Lyons PLC Brandy 1900, 1987 (Box EU7)
      - Beecham Group (Box EU7)
        - Margaret Astor cosmetics, 1989 (Box EU7)
        - Quorum by Puig men's fragrance, 1984 (Box EU7)
      - Distillers Company (Afersons, Johnny Walker Red scotch whiskey), 1986 (Box EU7)
      - Myrugia Group (Box EU7)
        - Armande perfume, 1988 (Box EU7)
        - Don Algodon clothing, 1988 (Box EU7)
        - Pinaud cosmetics, 1987 (Box EU7)
      - Quaker Oats (Fisher Price) toys, 1984 (Box EU7)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box EU7)
    - Madrid Office (Box EU7)
      - Bacardi (Box EU7)
        - Bacardi rum, 1984 (Box EU7)
        - Beefeater gin, 1984, 1987 (Box EU7)
      - [Banco Hispano Americano: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU7)
      - Banco Pastor, 1987 (Box EU7)
      - DeBeers, 1978, 1987 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU7)
      - Eastman Kodak (See also Oversize Box OV6, Oversize Folder OF14) (Box EU7)
        - EK6, 1977 (Box EU7)
        - Ektasound motion picture camera, 1974 (Box EU7)
        - Instamatic camera, undated (Box EU7)
        - Kodacolor film, 1987 (Box EU7)
      - Ediciones America Iberica (Biba), 1991 (Box EU7)
      - Ford (Box EU7)
        - Escort, 1987 (Box EU7)
        - Fiesta, 1976, 1980 (Box EU7)
        - Ford Service, 1978 (Box EU7)
        - Orion, 1984 (Box EU7)
      - Galerias Pzeciards, 1984, 1987 (Box EU7)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1970s-1990 (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU7)
      - Kraft (See also Oversize Folder OF14) (Box EU7)
        - Mayonase, 1973 (Box EU7)
        - Philadelphia Cream Cheese, 2002 (Box EU7)
        - Quintana cheese, 1984 (Box EU7)
        - Sante cheese products, 1985 (Box EU7)
        - Ziz cheese, 1976 (Box EU7)
      - Metro, 1984 (Box EU7)
      - [Ministry of Agriculture: See Oversize Box OV6] (Box EU7)
      - Nestlé (See also Oversize Box OV6) (Box EU7)
        - Mokanor instant coffee, 1977-1978 (Box EU7)
        - Nescafé instant coffee, 1973, 1976-1977, 1979 (Box EU7)
      - R.J. Reynolds (Winston), 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV6, Oversize Folder OF14) (Box EU7)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box EU7)
      - Scott Paper (Scottex), 1987 (Box EU7)
      - Unilever (Sunsilk) shampoo, 1978, 1980-1981 (Box EU7)
    - Undetermined Office (Box EU7)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (Box EU7)
  - Sweden (Stockholm Office) (Box EU7)
    - [Annousbolaget: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU8)
    - [Arlanda Airport: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU8)
    - Commodore International personal computers, 1985 (Box EU8)
    - Eastman Kodak (Box EU8)
      - Kodachrome film, 1984 (Box EU8)
      - Kodacolor film, 1984 (Box EU8)
      - Kodak Disc camera, 1984 (Box EU8)
    - Fortia A.B. pharmacy (Box EU8)
      - Laxerskolan, 1989 (Box EU8)
      - Popraven, 1988 (Box EU8)
      - Salazopurin, 1988 (Box EU8)
    - Glaxo Holdings, 1990 (Box EU8)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company (Swedish advertising campaigns, from Epcot Swap Shop), 1983-1984 (Box EU8)
    - Kellogg's Crunchy Nut Cornflakes, 1990 (Box EU8)
    - [Kemetyl: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU8)
    - Kraft (Box EU8)
      - Miracoli, 1990 (Box EU8)
      - Philadelphia cream cheese, 1985 (Box EU8)
      - Salad dressings, 1980 (Box EU8)
    - Kustartilleriet recruiting, 1984 (Box EU8)
    - [Marinstaben: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU8)
    - Mills mashed potatoes, 1981 (Box EU8)
    - Nestlé-Findus, 1991 (Box EU8)
    - Svenska Lakaresallkapet, 1989 (Box EU8)
    - Unilever (Box EU8)
      - Corall laundry detergent, 1984 (Box EU8)
      - Shield soap, 1982, 1988 (Box EU8)
      - Timotei shampoo, 1984 (Box EU8)
    - Warner-Lambert (Listerine), 1988 (Box EU8)
    - Warner-Lambert/Parke Davis (Box EU8)
      - Accupro, 1990 (Box EU8)
      - Lopid heart medicine, 1988, 1990 (Box EU8)
      - Vi-Siblin, 1989 (Box EU8)
  - Switzerland (Zurich Office) (Box EU8)
    - Actron security systems, 1990 (Box EU8)
    - Aer Lingus airline, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU8)
    - [AES (Schweiz): See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU8)
    - Cosmetica (Camelia) sanitary napkins, 1982 (Box EU8)
    - DeBeers, 1980s (Box EU8)
    - Eastman Kodak (Box EU8)
      - Consumer, 1964-1967 (Box EU8)
      - Trade, 1965-1966, 1971 (Box EU8)
    - Ford (Box EU8)
      - Capri, undated (Box EU8)
      - Escort XR3, undated (Box EU8)
      - Fiesta, undated (Box EU8)
      - Granada, undated (Box EU8)
      - Sierra, 1984 (Box EU8)
      - Taunus, undated (Box EU8)
      - Trucks, undated (Box EU8)
      - USA-Ford, undated (Box EU8)
      - Various products, Welcher Ford-typ bin ich?, 1981 (Box EU8)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company (Year-in-review collection), 1984 (Box EU8)
    - Kellogg Company (Box EU8)
      - Bran Buds, 1980-1981 (Box EU8)
      - Coco Krispies, 1980-1981 (Box EU8)
      - Corn Flakes, 1980-1981 (Box EU8)
      - Rice Krispies, 1980-1981 (Box EU8)
      - Top Form, 1980-1981 (Box EU8)
    - Maser Benedikt Textilwerke, 1984 (Box EU8)
    - R.J. Reynolds (Winston Mild), 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU8)
    - [SACOM: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU8)
    - Schweizerischer Obstverband (Opfelwii) cider, 1984 (Box EU8)
    - Unilever (Box EU8)
      - Corall detergent, circa 1983 (Box EU8)
      - FlyAway perfume, 1981 (Box EU8)
      - Gloria shampoo, 1988 (Box EU8)
      - Pepsodent toothpaste, 1980s (Box EU8)
    - Victor computers (Box EU8)
  - Turkey (Istanbul Office) (Box EU8)
    - [Altinyildiz: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU8)
    - IBM, 1980s (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU8)
  - United Kingdom (Box EU8)
    - London Office (Box EU8)
      - ABPI Pharmaceuticals (heart disease prevention), 1987 (Box EU9)
      - Air-Wick Ltd., 1954 (Box EU9)
      - ALCAN, 1968 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU9)
      - [Allied Lyons PLC: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU9)
      - Beecham (Campari), 1969 (Box EU9)
      - British Airports Authority, 1987 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU9)
      - British Railways Board, 1985 (Box EU9)
      - British Telecommunications Systems, 1985 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU9)
      - Burroughs Adding Machine Ltd., 1954 (Box EU9)
      - Butter Information Council, 1968-1969 (Box EU9)
      - Campbell's, 1968-1969 (Box EU9)
      - Cheese Bureau, 1969 (Box EU9)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1923-1963 (See also Oversize Box OV7), (6 folders) (Box EU9)
      - Cuticura Laboratories (Ayds Trimwheel exercise equipment), 1970 (Box EU9)
      - DeBeers, 1969-1997 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
      - De Vere Hotels, 1987 (Box EU10)
      - Eastman Kodak, trade, 1971 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
      - Europa Furniture, 1968 (Box EU10)
      - Findus frozen vegetables, 1968 (Box EU10)
        [See also Nestlé-Findus in other countries]
      - Ford (Escort, Orion), 1984 (Box EU10)
      - General Motors (Cadillac, Chevrolet trucks, from microfilm), 1920s (Box EU10)
      - Gallagher Amber Leaf, 1991 (Box EU10)
      - Gramco, 1970 (Box EU10)
      - [Grundig: See Oversize Folder OF15] (Box EU10)
      - Guiness, Arthur, Son, and Company, 1969 (Box EU10)
      - [Hi-Tee: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU10)
      - Horlicks sleep aid, 1932, 1968 (Box EU10)
        - Nulacin sleep aid, 1968 (Box EU10)
      - Insuramatic (Commercial stills), 1984 (Box EU10)
      - ITV Association, 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1957-1980s (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
      - [J&B scotch whiskey: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU10)
      - [Jaguar: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU10)
      - Kellogg Company (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
        - All-Bran, 1954, 1982-1984 (Box EU10)
        - Bran Buds, 1982-1983 (Box EU10)
        - Corn Flakes, 1983, 1988 (Box EU10)
        - Special K, 1983 (Box EU10)
      - Kraft (Box EU10)
        - Cheddar cheese, 1929 (Box EU10)
        - Ranch dressing, 1998 (Box EU10)
      - Lever Brothers (Lux flakes), 1900 (Box EU10)
      - [Madame Tussaud's: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU10)
      - Muscular Dystrophy Group, 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
      - [Observer, Ltd.: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU10)
      - Pan-American, 1954 (Box EU10)
      - Parker Pen Company, 1954, 1969 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
      - Quilted Fiesta, 1984 (Box EU10)
      - [ Reader's Digest: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU10)
      - Reckitt-Colman (Box EU10)
        - Colman's mustard, 1970 (Box EU10)
        - Sanpic disinfectant, 1954 (Box EU10)
      - [R.J. Reynolds: See Oversize Folder OF15] (Box EU10)
      - Rolex (with documentation), 1979, 1984, 1988 (Box EU10)
      - Rowntree Mackintosh (See also Oversize Box OV7, Oversize Folder OF15) (Box EU10)
        - General, 1952-1956 (Box EU10)
        - After Eight chocolate mints, 1969, 1980 (Box EU10)
        - Black Magic chocolates, 1933 (Box EU10)
        - KitKat, 1984-1991 (Box EU10)
        - Panyan (by Maconochie Brothers) pickles, 1968 (Box EU10)
        - Polo mints, 1984, 1989 (Box EU10)
        - Smarties, 1991 (Box EU10)
      - Royal Air Force, Central Office of Information, circa 1988 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU10)
      - Scott Paper Company (Scottie's) tissues, 1980-1981 (Box EU11)
      - Silhouette women's underwear, 1970 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - [Singer: See Oversize Folder OF15] (Box EU11)
      - Smith & Nephew Ltd. (Elastoplast) bandages, 1969 (Box EU11)
      - Standard Brands Ltd. (Royal) baking powder, 1954 (Box EU11)
      - Strongbow Ale, 1997 (Box EU11)
      - Swaddlers Togs children's clothes, 1989 (Box EU11)
      - Swakara, 1969 (Box EU11)
      - Thompson Holidays, 1984 (Box EU11)
      - Trustee Savings Bank Association, 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Tycom Corporation, 1982 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Unigate St. Ivel Gold, 1989 (Box EU11)
      - Unilever (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
        - Brooke Bond Oxo (Box EU11)
          - Fray Bentos, 1969, 1989 (Box EU11)
          - Oxo cubes, 1989 (Box EU11)
        - Elida Gibbs (Box EU11)
          - Harmony hair color, 1968 (Box EU11)
          - Sunwitch hair color, 1968 (Box EU11)
          - Timotei shampoo, 1984 (Box EU11)
        - Lux soap, 1932, 1934, 1954, 1990 (Box EU11)
        - Persil detergent, 1952-1956, 1984-1988, (2 folders) (Box EU11)
      - Warner-Lambert (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
        - Clorets, 1989 (Box EU11)
        - Listerine, 1981-1982 (Box EU11)
        - Mentholease lozenges, 1990 (Box EU11)
      - Wine and Spirit Association of Great Britain, 1953-1954, 1958-1959, 1961 (Box EU11)
    - Manchester Office (Box EU11)
      - ASDA Supermarkets, circa 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Baxi boilers, 1987-1991 (Box EU11)
      - [British Gas North Eastern: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU11)
      - Co-Operative Retail Services (Leo's Supermarkets), 1987-1989 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Greenwall Whitley Group PCC (Original Ale), 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Guardian and Manchester Evening News PLC, 1981, 1990 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Hanson PLC (New Era) homeopathic preparations, 1990 (Box EU11)
      - Holt Lloyd International PLC (Redex automotive engine cleaner), 1989 (Box EU11)
      - Magnet and Southerns, prefabricated kitchens, 1984 (Box EU11)
      - Norcross Ltd. (Cristal) ceramic tile, 1987-1988 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Northern Electric Company (Northern Telecom), 1988, 1990 (Box EU11)
      - [Piccadily Radio: See Oversize Box OV7] (Box EU11)
      - Pilkington Brothers eyeglasses, 1985, 1990 (Box EU11)
      - Sharp electronics (Computers, photocopiers, fax machines, calculators), 1987-1990 (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
      - Swinton Insurance Group, 1988-1989 (Box EU11)
      - Thorn EMI (Focus Multi Broadcast TV and Video), 1985 (Box EU11)
      - Warrington Runcorn (The Development Corporation), 1988 (Box EU11)
      - Yorkshire Building Society, 1988 (Box EU11)
    - Multiple Offices (Box EU11)
      - National Westminster Bank (See also Oversize Box OV7) (Box EU11)
        - Isle of Manchester Bank (Manchester Office), 1988 (Box EU11)
        - Natwest (London Office), 1969, 1984, 1987, 1989 (Box EU11)
- Latin America, 1928-2004 and undated (Box EU11)
  - Argentina (Buenos Aires Office) (Box EU11)
    - Asegurar insurance, 1989 (Box LA1)
    - Banelco bank card, 1988 (Box LA1)
    - Bausch & Lomb (Ray-Ban), 1984 (Box LA1)
    - B.F. Goodrich tires, 1930 (Box LA1)
    - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1990 (Box LA1)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's (Pond's Cold Creme, Vanishing Creme, Crema S, Angel Face), 1958-1963, (2 folders) (Box LA1)
    - Exxon (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA1)
      - Exxmar, 1987 (Box LA1)
      - Racing Sponsorship calendar, 1991 (Box LA1)
    - Ford (Box LA1)
      - Escort, 1987-1990 (Box LA1)
      - Sierra, 1984 (Box LA1)
    - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1980s (Box LA1)
    - Kelito chocolates, 1933 (Box LA1)
    - Nestlé instant coffee, 1989 (Box LA1)
    - Corbamil (New Balance) athletic shoes, 1989 (Box LA1)
    - Pan American, 1968-1969 (Box LA1)
    - Rolex (some from photocopies), 1968, 1990 (Box LA1)
    - Seagrams Robert Brown's whiskey, 1969 (Box LA1)
  - Bermuda (Undetermined Office) (Box LA1)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1928, 1931, (2 folders) (Box LA1)
  - Bolivia (La Paz Office) (Box LA1)
    - Cerveceria Nacional de Bolivia (Nacional brand beer), 1978 (Box LA1)
  - Brazil (Box LA1)
    - Rio de Janeiro Office (Box LA1)
      - Atlantic Refining Company of Brazil, 1969 (Box LA2)
      - CADAM (Caulim Da Amazonia S.A.) mining, 1984 (Box LA2)
      - Coleção Diamantes, 1981 (Box LA2)
      - DeBeers, 1983-1984 (Box LA2)
      - Exxon Esso, 1987 (Box LA2)
      - Globo Editora publishing, 1987 (Box LA2)
      - Kraft (Philadelphia Cream Cheese), 2003-2004 (Box LA2)
      - Nabisco Brands (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA2)
        [See also Standard Brands elsewhere in this collection]
        - Royal baking powder, undated (Box LA2)
        - Royal desserts, 1989 (Box LA2)
      - PepsiCo, 1985 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA2)
      - Undetermined Client, 1987 (Box LA2)
    - São Paulo Office (Box LA2)
      - Blue Star Line (from microfilm), 1930 (Box LA2)
      - [Champion spark Plug: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA2)
      - Eastman Kodak Kodakcolor VR film, 1980-1996 (See also Oversize Box OV8, Oversize Folder OF16) (Box LA2)
      - Ford, 1961-1987 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA2)
        [Includes Escort, XR3, Tractors, Trucks, JWT publication Ford Truck Line News (1984) from the EPCOT swap shop]
      - Giroflex office furniture, 1985, 1987 (Box LA2)
      - Heublein (Liebfraumilch), undated (Box LA2)
      - J. Walter Thompson Company, 1980s (Box LA2)
      - Johnson Motors (Sea-Horse outboard motors, from microfilm; See also Outboard Marine), 1930 (Box LA2)
      - Lorenzetti Group, 1989 (Box LA2)
      - Maguary fruit juice, 1969 (Box LA2)
      - NCR computers, 1984, 1986 (Box LA2)
      - Nestlé baby food, 1988 (Box LA2)
      - Philips (See also Oversize Box OV8, Oversize Folder OF16) (Box LA2)
        - Odyssey computer game system, 1984 (Box LA2)
        - Products De Ultima Geracao styling appliances, 1989 (Box LA2)
      - Refinacoes de Milho, 1931 (from microfilm) (Box LA2)
      - Rolex, 1986 (Box LA2)
      - Sao Paulo Alpargatas (Topper Brand) athletic shoes, 1984, 1986 (Box LA2)
      - Unilever (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA2)
        - Atkinsons, Locao de Beleza (hair remover), 1988 (Box LA2)
        - Gessy Lever, SEDA, 1988 (Box LA2)
        - Lever Soap, 1950-1955 (Box LA2)
        - Lux, 1988 (Box LA2)
      - Warner-Lambert (Clorets), 1988 (Box LA2)
    - Multiple Offices (Box LA2)
      - Citicorp (Box LA2)
        - Citibank (Rio de Janeiro), 1984 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA2)
        - Mastercard (Sao Paulo), 1987-1988 (Box LA2)
        - Visa (São Paulo), 1986 (Box LA2)
          [Promoting tourism for viewing Halley's Comet]
    - Undetermined Office (Box LA2)
      - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA2)
      - [Cigarros Souza Cruz: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA2)
  - Chile (Santiago Office) (Box LA2)
    - AFP Summa insurance and investment Services, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - [Banco O'Higgins: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA3)
    - Banco Sud Americano (Box LA3)
      - Banking Services, 1990 (Box LA3)
      - Corfinsa, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - British American Tobacco (Box LA3)
      - Advance, 1984 (Box LA3)
      - Derby, 1980s (Box LA3)
    - Centenario Ltda. (Hucke) chocolates, 1990 (Box LA3)
    - Cervecerias Unidas Momento para una cerveca campaign, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1962 (Box LA3)
    - Cidere Biobio Regional Development Authority, 1989-1990 (Box LA3)
    - [Compania de Papeles y Cartones: See Oversize Box OV8] (Box LA3)
    - Compania Industrial (Chef Brand) cooking oil, circa 1988 (Box LA3)
    - CoopAgricole Pisquera Elqui (Box LA3)
      - Capel, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - Pisco Control, 1990 (Box LA3)
    - Eastman Kodak (Box LA3)
      - Fling camera, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - Kodacolor film, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - Kodak paper, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - Kodak videotape, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - S Series camera, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - Holiday Inn Crowne Plaza, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - IBM, 1988, 1990 (Box LA3)
    - Lan Chile Airline, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - Lanas Cisne (Bottoncito, Magic, Mohair Superstar, Sinfonia brand wools), 1990 (Box LA3)
    - Nestlé (Box LA3)
      - Chambourey yogurt, 1987 (Box LA3)
      - Findus frozen dinners, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - Maggi frozen vegetables, 1990 (Box LA3)
      - Nestlé Chocolates, 1989 (Box LA3)
    - Parker Pen Company, 1986-1987 (Box LA3)
    - Philips (household electriconics and appliances), 1989-1990 (Box LA3)
    - Prompan Bakery (El Pan de Hoy campaign), 1989 (See also Oversize Box OV8) (Box LA3)
    - Provense Ltda. (Apumanque) department store, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - Raycass (L'Asst) pantyhose, 1988 (Box LA3)
    - Saroma instant fruit juice, 1987 (Box LA3)
    - Sociedad Aeronautica de Medellin (SAM), 1987 (Box LA3)
    - Suizer yogurt, 1980s (Box LA3)
    - Unilever (Box LA3)
      - Astra soap, 1980s (Box LA3)
      - Clinic hair care, 1987 (Box LA3)
      - Close-Up toothpaste, 1980s (Box LA3)
      - Denim shampoo, 1980s (Box LA3)
      - Korall detergent, 1988 (Box LA3)
      - Lux soap, 1980s (Box LA3)
      - Pepsodent toothpaste, 1972, 1980s (Box LA3)